Guide to the Records of National Conference on Soviet Jewry, undated, 1949, 1954, 1956, 1958-1993 *I-181 and *I-181A
American Jewish Historical Society, Newton Centre, MA and New York, NY
- Part 2, Series XI: Summit Meetings, International Soviet Jews and Human Rights Conferences, undated, 1973-1991; Boxes 297-314.
  - Subseries B: Conferences and other events, undated, 1975-1991; Boxes 301-314.
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Certificates (Box 312, Folder 14)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Follow-up Notes, Pleas, Suggestions (Box 312, Folder 15)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Letters of Invitation and Responses, 1982-1983 (Box 312, Folder 16)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Messages From Congress and the Administration (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Papers and Presentations (Box 313, Folder 2)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Planning, Congress and Administration Participation, Invites, Thank You Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 313, Folder 3)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Planning, Funding, 1982-1983 (Box 313, Folder 4)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Planning, General Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 313, Folder 5)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Planning, Interfaith Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 313, Folder 6)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Planning, NCSJ Mailings, 1982-1983 (Box 313, Folder 7)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Planning, Program, 1982 (Box 313, Folder 8)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Planning, Steering Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 313, Folder 9)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Planning, Supporting Communities, 1982-1983 (Box 313, Folder 10)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Planning, Travel Arrangements, 1982-1983 (Box 313, Folder 11)
    - Third International Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, March 1983 -- Publicity and Press (Box 313, Folder 12)
    - Various Conferences on Soviet Jewry, undated, 1969-1970, 1979, 1982-1983, 1986 (Box 313, Folder 13)
    - World Conference of Jewish Communities on Soviet Jewry, Brussels, February 23-25, 1971 (Box 313, Folder 14)
    - World Conference on Soviet Jewry, Brussels [1 of 2], February 17-19, 1976 (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - World Conference on Soviet Jewry, Brussels [2 of 2], February 17-19, 1976 (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - World Conference on Soviet Jewry, Jerusalem, 1988-1989 (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - World Conference on Soviet Jewry Leader Assembly -- Resolutions, 1983-1985 (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - World Conference on Soviet Jewry, London, October 1983 -- Presidium (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - World Conference on Soviet Jewry, Paris, 1989 -- Professionals Meeting (Box 314, Folder 6)
- Part 2, Series XII: Soviet Jewry and ASJM Information Materials (publications, newsletters, clippings), undated, 1952, 1961-1992; Boxes 315-330.
  This series is devoted to publications, newsletters and clippings found within the collection and dedicated to writings regarding the Soviet Jewry Movement. The Series is divided into two Subseries: Subseries A: Newsletters, undated, 1963-1989 and Subseries B: Publications and related materials, undated, 1965-1987.
  - Subseries A: Newsletters, undated, 1963-1992; Boxes 315-322.
    - 35's (Women's Campaign for Soviet Jewry, London, UK), 1987 (with gaps) (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - 35's (Women's Campaign for Soviet Jewry, London, UK), 1988 (with gaps) (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - 35's (Women's Campaign for Soviet Jewry, London, UK), 1989 (with gaps) (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - Activities Report (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, NY), 1976-1977; (3 issues) (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - Century and Peace (Soviet Peace Committee), 1986-1987; (3 issues) (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - Current History (Current History, Inc., Philadelphia, PA), December 1987-March 1988 (Box 315, Folder 6)
    - Current History (Current History, Inc., Philadelphia, PA), March 1989-May 1989 (Box 315, Folder 7)
    - Currents (Greater New York Conference on Soviet Jewry), 1981-1982 (Box 315, Folder 8)
    - Digest: A Periodic Review (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, Washington, D.C.), 1986-1987 (with gaps) (Box 315, Folder 9)
    - Exit Visa (Association of Jewish Ex-Servicemen & Women, London, UK), 1987-1988; (3 issues) (Box 315, Folder 10)
    - Focus Soviet Jewry (The Israel Public Council for Soviet Jewry, World Zionist Organization, Tel Aviv, Israel), 1987-1989 (Box 315, Folder 11)
    - Freedom at Issue (Freedom House, NY), 1987-1988 (with gaps) (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - Freedom Monitor (Freedom House, NY), 1987; (2 copies) (Box 316, Folder 2)
    - Gli Ebrei Nell'Europa Orientale (Inconto di Giuristi Europei, Rome, Italy), 1972, 1974; (2 issues) (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - Help & Action (Help & Action, Hericy, France), 1987 (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - Help & Action (Help & Action, Hericy, France), 1988; (2 issues) (Box 316, Folder 5)
    - Informatsionnyi Biulleten' po Voprosam Repatriatsii I Evreiskoi Kul'tury (Informational Bulletin on the Questions of Repatriation and Jewish Culture) (Jewish Information Center in Moscow), 1988 (with gaps) (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - Insight: Soviet Jews (European Jewish Publications Ltd., London, UK), 1975-1977 (Box 317, Folder 1)
    - Insight: Soviet Jews (European Jewish Publications Ltd., London, UK), 1978-1981 (with gaps) (Box 317, Folder 2)
    - Insight: Soviet Jews (European Jewish Publications Ltd., London, UK), 1982-1986 (with gaps) (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - International Newsletter (International Committee for Soviet and East European Studies, Paris, France), 1986-1987; (2 issues) (Box 317, Folder 4)
    - Jewish Currents (Association for Promotion of Jewish Secularism, Inc., NY), 1987; (2 issues) (Box 317, Folder 5)
    - Jews in Eastern Europe: A Periodical Survey of Events (European Jewish Publications Ltd., London, UK), 1963-1966 (Box 317, Folder 6)
    - Jews in Eastern Europe: A Periodical Survey of Events (European Jewish Publications Ltd., London, UK), 1967-1969 (Box 317, Folder 7)
    - Jews in Eastern Europe: A Periodical Survey of Events (European Jewish Publications Ltd., London, UK), 1970-1974 (Box 317, Folder 8)
    - Jews in the USSR (National Council for Soviet Jewry of the United Kingdom and Ireland, London, UK), 1987-1989 (with gaps) (Box 317, Folder 9)
    - JTA Daily News Bulletin (Jewish Telegraphic Agency, NY), 1988 (with gaps) (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Juden in Der UDSSR (Aktionsgemeinschaft für die Juden in der Sowietunion, Zürich, Germany), 1988-1989 (with gaps) (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Keeping Posted (Union of American Hebrew Congregations, NY), 1972, 1976; (2 issues) (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Les Procès De Juifs En Union Soviètique (Bibliothèque Juive Contemporaine, Paris, France), 1970-1971; (5 issues) (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - NCSJ Congressional Update (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, Washington, D.C.), 1988; (6 issues) (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - Near East Report (Near East Research, Inc., Washington, D.C.), 1987-1989 (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - New American (Committee for the Absorption of Soviet Emigres, New American Federal Credit Union, NJ), 1986-1987 (with gaps) (Box 318, Folder 7)
    - News Bulletin (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, NY), 1973-1974 (Box 318, Folder 8)
    - News Bulletin (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, NY), 1975-1976 (Box 318, Folder 9)
    - News Bulletin (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, NY), 1977-1978 (Box 318, Folder 10)
    - News Bulletin (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, NY), 1979 (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - Newsbreak (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, Washington, D.C.), 1986-1988 (with gaps) (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - Newsbreak (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, Washington, D.C.), 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 3)
    - Newsbreak (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, Washington, D.C.), 1991-1992 (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Newsletter of the American Jewish Conference on Soviet Jewry (American Jewish Conference on Soviet Jewry, NY), October 1971 (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - Newsletter on Jews in the Soviet Union (American Jewish Conference on Soviet Jewry, NY), 1972 (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - Newsline (Greater New York Conference on Soviet Jewry), 1981-1982 (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - Press Service (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, New York, NY), January 1981-September 1981 (Box 319, Folder 8)
    - Press Service (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, New York, NY), October 1981-1982 (Box 319, Folder 9)
    - Press Service (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, New York, NY), December 1982-August 1983 (Box 319, Folder 10)
    - Prisoner Bulletin (International Representation for the Council of Evangelical Baptist Churches of the Soviet Union, Inc., Elkhart, IN), 1988-1989; (4 issues) (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Research Report (Institute of Jewish Affairs in Association with the World Jewish Congress, London, UK), 1981-1987 (with gaps) (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Research Report (Institute of Jewish Affairs in Association with the World Jewish Congress, London, UK), 1988-1989 (with gaps) (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Smoloskyp (Helsinki Guarantees for Ukraine Committee and the Ukrainian Information Service), 1987-1988 (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - Soviet East European Report (Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty, Washington, D.C.), 1987-1988 (with gaps) (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Jewish Affairs (Institute of Jewish Affairs), 1971, 1973-1974 (with gaps) (Box 320, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Jewish Affairs (Institute of Jewish Affairs), 1975-1977, 1980 (with gaps) (Box 320, Folder 7)
    - Soviet Jewish Affairs (Institute of Jewish Affairs), 1982-1984 (with gaps) (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - Soviet Jewish Affairs (Institute of Jewish Affairs), 1985-1986, 1989 (with gaps) (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Soviet Labour Review (Russian Research Foundation, London, UK), 1986-1988 (with gaps) (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Surviving Together: A Journal on Soviet-American Relations (Institute for Soviet-American Relations), 1986 (with gaps) (Box 321, Folder 3)
    - Surviving Together: A Journal on Soviet-American Relations (Institute for Soviet-American Relations), 1987 (with gaps) (Box 321, Folder 4)
    - Surviving Together: A Journal on Soviet-American Relations (Institute for Soviet-American Relations), 1988, 1992; (3 issues) (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - The Caucasus Network (The Caucasus Network, NY), 1987-1989 (with gaps) (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - The Samizdat Bulletin (Samizdat Publications, Inc., Center for Democracy, CA), 1987-1988 (with gaps) (Box 321, Folder 7)
    - The Task (The National Interreligious Task Force on Soviet Jewry, IL), 1987-1988 (with gaps) (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Un Mois Avec Les Juifs D'USSR (Bibliothèque Juive Contemporaine, Paris, France), 1987-1988 (with gaps) (Box 322, Folder 2)
    - U.S.-Soviet Outlook (American Committee on US-Soviet Relations, Washington, D.C.), 1987-1988 (with gaps) (Box 322, Folder 3)
    - USSR News Brief: Human Rights (Das Land Und Die Welt e. V., München, Germany), 1986-1988 (with gaps) (Box 322, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Newsletters (Single Issues), 1973, 1979, 1985 (Box 322, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Newsletters (Single Issues), 1987-1989 (Box 322, Folder 6)
  - Subseries B: Publications and related materials, undated, 1952, 1961-1962, 1964-1965, 1967-1988; Boxes 323-330.
    - A Study of Jews Refused Their Right to Leave the Soviet Union, Volume II, Part 1, December 1981 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Articles and Publications on Refuseniks and Prisoners of Conscience, 1980-1983 (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - Articles and Publications on Refuseniks and Prisoners of Conscience, 1984 (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Articles and Publications on Refuseniks and Prisoners of Conscience, 1985-1987 (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - Case Histories of the Refuseniks, August 1976, Contains Orphans of the Exodus: Separated Soviet Jewish Families, A Collection of Case Histories, by Margery Sanford (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Case Histories of the Refuseniks, March 1977 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - Case Histories of the Refuseniks, October 1977 (Box 323, Folder 7)
    - Case Histories of the Refuseniks, December 1977 (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Case Histories of the Refuseniks, Volume V, August 1978 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Case Histories of the Refuseniks, Volume VI, August 1979 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Case Histories of the Refuseniks, Volume VII, October 1980 (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Case Histories of the Refuseniks, Volume VIII, September 1981 (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Case Histories of the Refuseniks, Volume IX, September 1982 (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Case Histories of the Refuseniks, Volume XI, September 1984 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Curriculum on Soviet Jewry, 1983 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Drafts of "They're Out" Booklet, 1979-1980 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Language Pamphlets and Articles Regarding Soviet Jews, 1965, 1971-1972 (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Language Pamphlets and Articles Regarding Soviet Jews, 1973 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Language Pamphlets and Articles Regarding Soviet Jews, 1974, 1976, 1978, 1980 (Box 325, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Language Pamphlets and Articles Regarding Soviet Jews, 1981, 1983-1985 (Box 325, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Language Pamphlets and Articles Regarding Soviet Jews, 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Language Pamphlets and Articles Regarding Soviet Jews, undated, 1987 (Box 325, Folder 9)
    - Guidelines for Corresponding with Soviet Jews, 1982-1985 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - How the USSR Supreme Soviet Functions, by Lev Tolkunov, 1987 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - Howard M. Sachar Manuscripts -- "Frankenstein Utopia," "The Jews of Protest," "Hostages of Détente", 1983 (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Materials in Russian Language, 1979-1981, 1986 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Soviet Jews, 1962, 1964-1965, 1970 (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Soviet Jews, 1971 (Box 326, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Soviet Jews, 1972-1973 (Box 326, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Soviet Jews, 1974-1976 (Box 326, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Soviet Jews, 1977 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Soviet Jews, 1978-1980 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Soviet Jews, 1981 (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Soviet Jews, 1982-1985 (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Soviet Jews, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Articles Regarding Soviet Union From America and Europe, 1961, 1965, 1967-1970, 1972, 1975-1976 (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Articles Regarding Soviet Union From America and Europe, 1977-1980 (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Articles Regarding Soviet Union From America and Europe, undated, 1981-1983 (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Articles Regarding Soviet Union From America and Europe, undated, 1984-1986 (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Articles Regarding Soviet Union From America and Europe, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - Orphans of the Exodus: Separated Soviet Jewish Families, A Collection of Case Histories, by Margery Sanford, 1976 (Box 328, Folder 5)
    - Perspectives on Soviet Jewry, Nathan Glazer et al., 1971; I Am a Jew: Essays on Jewish Identity in the Soviet Union, 1973; Jews and Jewish Topics in Soviet and East-European Publications (Hebrew University of Jerusalem) (Box 328, Folder 6)
    - Program/Seminar Materials on Jewish Culture in the USSR, 1977-1978 (Box 329, Folder 1)
    - Program/Seminar Materials on Jewish Culture in the USSR, undated, 1979-1980 (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - Proposed Films, Filmstrips, Audiovisual Aid, Posters, includes "Sound of the Great Shofar..." Poster (see also OS1 folder, item I-181A.006), 1974-1979, 1981, 1984 (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - Proposed Films, Filmstrips, Audiovisual Aid, Posters, includes "Everyone of Them Needs Everyone of Us..." Poster (see also OS1 folder, item I-181A.007), undated, 1986 (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - Scripts, Dramatic Readings, Services, Presentations, 1965, 1967-1970, 1975-1978 (Box 329, Folder 5)
    - Scripts, Dramatic Readings, Services, Presentations, includes two Audiocassettes), 1981-1983 (Box 329, Folder 6)
    - Scripts, Dramatic Readings, Services, Presentations, includes "Let My People Go" Postcard, undated, 1984-1986 (Box 329, Folder 7)
    - Soviet Jewry Program Guide (South Florida Conference on Soviet Jewry), 1982 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - Special Program Materials with Printed Plastic Bag (see also OS1 folder, item I-181A.005), 1977, 1979-1980 (Box 330, Folder 2)
    - Special Program Materials, 1982 (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - Special Program Materials with "Sealed but not Delivered Poster and Farewell Moscow film information (see also OS1 folder, item I-181A.004), undated, 1986-1988 (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - Stuart Hample Play Script, 1983 (Box 330, Folder 5)
    - The Anatomy of a Protest, by Rabbi Haskel Lookstein, 1982; The Bloodshed Unites Us, Wladyslaw Bartoszewski, 1970; Russian Sketches by Shelomo ben-Israel, 1967, 1967, 1970, 1982 (Box 330, Folder 6)
    - "White Book of Exodus" (National Conference on Soviet Jewry, NY), 1972 (Box 330, Folder 7)
    - Why They Left: A Survey of Soviet Jewish Emigrants, by Maurice Friedberg, 1972; August 12, 1952: Night of the Murdered Poets by Carol R. Saivetz et al., 1973; "Soviet Jewry and the Implementation of the Helsinki Final Act," Report, 1977; Immigration to Israel., 1952, 1972-1973, 1977 (Box 330, Folder 8)
- Part 2, Series XIII: Human Rights, U.S. Politics, International Politics, anti-Semitism and Holocaust, USSR Politics, General Information Materials, undated, 1949, 1954, 1956, 1958-1991; Boxes 331-360.
  Arranged into five subseries.
  This series includes general information regarding human rights, U.S., USSR and International politics, Soviet propaganda, anti-Semitism and the Holocaust. The Series is divided into five Subseries as follows: Subseries A: U.S. Politics, undated, 1949, 1966, 1970-1988; Subseries B: Soviet Politics and Propaganda, undated, 1954, 1956, 1958-1988; Subseries C: Human Rights and International Politics, undated, 1958, 1963-1964, 1968-1990; Subseries D: Soviet Propaganda Campaign Letters ("Varvariv letters"), 1979; and Subseries E: U.S-USSR relations, undated, 1964, 1976-1990.
  - Subseries A: U.S. Politics, undated, 1949, 1966, 1970-1974, 1976-1989; Boxes 331-332.
    - Articles and Publications on USA Immigration Policies, undated, 1976, 1979-1981 (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - Articles and Publications on USA Immigration Policies, undated, 1982-1984, 1988 (Box 331, Folder 2)
    - Emergency Committee for American Trade, 1979 (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Affairs, Spring 1989 (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - Immigration and Nationality Act, 7th Edition (Committee on the Judiciary House of Representatives, United States), 1980 (Box 331, Folder 5)
    - Jackson-Vanik Amendment, 1973, 1977-1985 (Box 331, Folder 6)
    - Jackson-Vanik Amendment, undated, 1986-1988 (Box 331, Folder 7)
    - McClure Amendment, 1988 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Most Favored Nation Status-Romania, 1985-1988 (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - Reagan and Carter Proposed Policy Regarding USSR, 1980-1981 (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - Stevenson Amendment, 1978-1979 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Policy Toward Human Rights in the USSR and Other Countries, 1949, 1966, 1970-1972, 1974, 1976 (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Policy Toward Human Rights in the USSR and Other Countries, 1977-1980 (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Policy Toward Human Rights in the USSR and Other Countries, 1981-1984 (Box 332, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Policy Toward Human Rights in the USSR and Other Countries, undated, 1985 (Box 332, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B: Soviet Politics and Propaganda, undated, 1954, 1956, 1958-1974, 1976-1989, 1991; Boxes 333-349.
    - Analogy of Judophobia in Nazi and Soviet Anti-Semitic Cartoons, undated, 1978 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Analysis of Soviet Anti-Zionist Publications by Yehoshua Yakhot, undated (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Andropov, Yuri, 1982-1984 (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Anti-Semitism in USSR, undated, 1984-1987 (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - Anti-Zionist Committee in the USSR, 1983-1984 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - Anti-Zionist Committees in the USSR, 1985-1988 (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Appeals to 26th Congress of CPSU, 1981 (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - Articles on Soviet Anti-Semitism, 1969, 1971-1974, 1977 (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - Articles on Soviet Anti-Semitism, 1978 (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Articles on Soviet Anti-Semitism, 1979-1981 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - Articles on Soviet Anti-Semitism, 1982-1984 (Box 334, Folder 6)
    - Articles on Soviet Anti-Semitism, 1985-1986 (Box 334, Folder 7)
    - Articles on Soviet Anti-Semitism, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Birobidzhan, undated, 1977, 1979-1980, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - "Black Book" on Holocaust in the USSR Territory, 1984-1986 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Chernobyl Nuclear Accident in the USSR, 1986 (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - Christian Religion in USSR, 1978-1985, 1988 (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Constitution of the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1977 (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - CPSU-26th Party Congress, 1976, 1981, 1986 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Decline of Emigration from USSR Since 1980, 1979-1984 (Box 335, Folder 8)
    - Dissent in the Soviet Union, 1977-1980, 1983-1987 (Box 335, Folder 9)
    - Donetsk Trial, 1978-1980 (Box 335, Folder 10)
    - Exit Tax, undated, 1971-1973 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - Forced Labor in the USSR, 1978, 1980-1982 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - Forced Labor in the USSR, March 1983-May 1983 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Forced Labor in the USSR, November 1983 (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - Forced Labor in the USSR, December 1983 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Forced Labor in the USSR, 1984-1986 (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - Forced Labor in the USSR, undated, 1987 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - Freidberg, Maurice, 1964-1966 (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - Glasnost Policy in the USSR, 1987 (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Gorbachev's Visit to the UN, 1988 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Government-USSR, 1976-1983 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Hebrew Teachers in USSR, 1979-1980, 1984-1985 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Intourist, 1984-April 1986 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Intourist, May-November 1986 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Intourist, undated, 1987 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Culture in the USSR, 1977-1979 (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - Jewish Culture in the USSR, undated, 1980-1985, 1989 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Emigration from the USSR, 1972, 1976-1979 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Emigration from the USSR, 1980-1981 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Emigration from the USSR, 1982 (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - Jewish Emigration from the USSR, 1983-1985 (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - Jewish Emigration from the USSR, 1986 (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Emigration from the USSR, undated, 1987 (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Emigration from the USSR, 1988-1989 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Religion in USSR, undated, 1977, 1979-1980, 1983, 1985-1986 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - Jews in the Soviet Press, 1985-1986 (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Jews in the USSR-Figures, Facts, Comments, 1982 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - KGB Interrogation of Robert Toth, 1977 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - KGB, 1977, 1980, 1982-1984, 1986-1987 (Box 339, Folder 6)